{
  "extraDescription": "Convert exact decimal expansions to fractions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{2}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "20/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.\\overline{857142}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "41/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.25\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "17/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.1\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "31/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.3\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "53/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{4}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "13/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.8\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "5/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.\\overline{428571}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "38/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.2\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "21/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.6\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.5\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.\\overline{571428}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "39/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.25\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "5/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "7/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.75\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "15/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.\\overline{2}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "29/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.\\overline{5}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "32/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.8\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "9/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.25\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.1\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "13/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.6\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "23/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{714285}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "5/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.875\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "31/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.\\overline{8}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "44/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.\\overline{571428}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "32/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{1}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "1/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{142857}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "8/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "11/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{571428}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.1\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "7/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.75\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "23/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{142857}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "1/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.9\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "9/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.\\overline{142857}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "29/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.3\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "43/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.125\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "9/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.5\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "9/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.1\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "25/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.25\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "13/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.4\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "7/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{285714}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "16/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.75\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "11/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.875\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "39/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{428571}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "10/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.8\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "14/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.125\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "25/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.7\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "27/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "16/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.375\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "3/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.\\overline{7}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "34/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.6\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "28/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.8\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "19/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.4\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "22/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.4\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "12/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.125\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "33/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.4\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "17/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.25\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "9/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.9\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "29/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{428571}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "17/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.4\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{1}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "10/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.5\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "7/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.2\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "16/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.875\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "7/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.625\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "5/8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [8]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.2\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "6/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{5}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "23/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{714285}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "12/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{285714}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "9/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.5\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.8\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "24/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{2}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "2/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "14/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.75\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{2}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "11/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "8/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.6\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "18/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.1\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "19/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "17/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.\\overline{142857}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "36/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1.\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "4/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{7}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "25/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.4\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "27/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.\\overline{285714}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "2/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.\\overline{857142}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "20/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.\\overline{857142}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "27/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [7]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(0.8\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.8\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "35/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.1\\overline{6}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "31/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.8\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "29/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.2\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "26/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.7\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "47/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [10]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.\\overline{4}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "40/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [9]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2.5\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5.5\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "11/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4.\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "13/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3.8\\overline{3}\\) to fraction in simplest form",
      "answer": "23/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [6]
    }
  ]
}
